addoway.com 2018-05-17

# Addoway - Privacy Policy

By becoming a member of Addoway.com you are agreeing to have your email address; contact information; account activity when bidding, selling, and/or buying; shipping and billing information you provide when completing a transaction; chat and discussion data including but not limited to ratings of other buyer/sellers; statistical analysis on page visits; IP address; traffic to and from the site; and information from other companies giving us demographic and traffic data collected and stored by our servers located in the United States. We treat all information on our servers as critically important data and will go through every effort to ensure your privacy and security. Third parties may illegally intercept information during your time with Addoway.com and we therefore cannot promise that your information will always be safe and private from these unlawful parties, but we make every effort to do everything possible on our side to stay protected and keep these third parties out.

Addoway.com will not in any way sell or rent your information to any organization for any use at all unless you give prior explicit consent. We may use this information to help us improve the site content for marketing and advertising purposes. All users have the option of opting out of marketing contacts in their user profile. All information given to Addoway.com to create an account to buy and/or sell will be kept in strict confidentiality and kept secure with the latest technology. Personal information is collected solely to provide you with a safe and efficient online experience.

At Addoway.com you can trust that your information is kept secure and safe. Please see rules under statistical data for any questions regarding our question when creating a new account. Users must take full responsibility of all information on their account and assume responsibility for unlawful access into their account. Users must make every effort to use secure networks and preferably access from home to reduce the chances of account login and password information being stolen. Please contact us immediately if you discover any suspicious activities or violations of the terms & conditions stated here. We may disclose personal information in response to illegal activities to law enforcement if any content violates the rights of other members. We will never ask you to verify account information via email or phone. All contact from Addoway and its users is strictly done through your profile.   
 **  
** Addoway.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this Site. We use collected information to provide or improve Services for Users, and as more particularly set forth above, we may use collected information to contact Users for a variety of reasons, including, without limitation, obtaining information from Users regarding their use of the Site and Services and ways we can improve them, and to send information to them regarding us, our Services, or our Partners, such as promotions and events. We use this information in ways we determine appropriate in our sole discretion, and we reserve the right to do so. We will not sell or rent personally identifiable information to anyone, and we will not disclose any collected information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement.  

  Addoway.com collects personally identifiable information when you register for an Addoway.com account, when you use certain Addoway.com products or services, and when you visit Addoway.com pages. Addoway.com may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners. 

  When you register with Addoway.com, we ask for personally identifiable information including, but not limited to, your name, email address, address, and zip code. Once you register with Addoway.com and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us. Addoway.com also automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser including your IP address, Addoway.com cookie information, and the page you requested. 

  **Statistical Data**

When you add yourself to the Addoway.com database you are asked a question regarding your online purchasing experience. This information is only gathered for statistical purposes to understand the population of users that come to Addoway.com and will not be sold or rented in any way to any organization. All personal information will be also kept confidential to protect privacy. Please strive in every way to keep your computer and internet connections safe and secure as we will not be responsible for account information being stolen due to comprises from the users lack of personal precautions.

**Protect Yourself Online and Prevent Fraud  ** 

1.  Never reply to emails that ask for personal information verification. Please report all spam emails like this to [spam@addoway.com](mailto:spam@addoway.com). If you receive an email from Addoway.com you will also be able to read this email via your personal account at www.addoway.com. We will never contact you and ask you to verify personal information.

2.  Keep a close eye on your personal accounts. Credit bureau reports should be run annually for everyone to verify all information is correct and valid.

3.  In the event of identity theft; please follow the proper procedures to protect yourself and your credit. The three major credit bureaus are listed below, so please feel free to utilize this information in the event that you want to check your credit history.   

**Equifax  **[www.equifax.com](http://pricebeats.com/privacy/%5C)   
Reporting fraud: 1-800-525-6285   
Ordering report: 1-800-685-1111

**Experian  **[www.experian.com ](http://pricebeats.com/privacy/%5C)   
Reporting fraud: 1-888-397-3742   
Ordering report: 1-888-397-3742

**TransUnion  **[www.tuc.com ](http://pricebeats.com/privacy/%5C)   
Reporting fraud: 1-800-680-7289   
Ordering report: 1-800-916-8800 

4.  Never give your password to anyone at anytime. We suggest passwords that are strong in nature containing both alpha and numeric characters. We also suggest changing your password often.

5.  Keep your firewall turned on; keep your operating system up-to-date; use updated antivirus software; and use updated antispyware technology. See <http://www.microsoft.com/protect/default.mspx>[ ](http://www.microsoft.com/protect/default.mspx)for more information on keeping your PC safe.  

6.  Know your seller. Read all comments and pay specific attention to user comments on communication. Understand the users return policy if any applies. If there is a deal that sounds too good to be true, then it is probably too good to be true! Communicate openly and understand expectations. If you have a question, please ask. Ask for tracking numbers as soon as the product is shipped.  

7.  Know your buyer. Abnormal requests can be a sign up suspicious activity. Are they requesting to pay it from multiple PayPal accounts? What is their member rating? Communicate with the buyer through the instant messenger format in your my profile section. Make sure you have open lines of communication before sending your products. Once you receive tracking numbers send them directly to the client and if you can insure the products, please do so to protect yourself in the event the buyer indicates they never received your item. The most important step is to set expectations and communicate with the buyer.

8.  Addoway.com has been created to facilitate in the buying/selling transaction process. We promote a safe and fun transaction environment. Buying and/or selling outside of Addoway.com is done at users own risk! Use our services.  

Please be advised that our privacy policy can change at any time, so please continue to check back from time to time. If we make any substantial changes we will ensure that we create an announcement posting on the site.

Thank you,

Team Addoway

If you have any questions about any information listed on Addoway please contact: membersupport@addoway.com
